The Carrier is a action, thriller, science fiction
film directed by Anthony Woodley.
England has been overrun by a pandemic with no apparent cure.
As the infection continues to spread, safety - for a lucky few - looms
in the form of a damaged 747 set to seek solace abroad.
It's only once the plane is airborne that the survivors discover
the infection made it onto the flight with them.
Craig Turnpike, played by Jack Gordon.
Tobias Black, played by Edmund Kingsley.
Eric Mason, played by Joe Dixon.
Terri Holmes, played by Josie Taylor.
Maria Adams, played by Karen Bryson.
Second Lieutenant Harvey, played by Nikolaos Brahimllari.
The Carrier is a 2015 British science fiction thriller film directed by Anthony
Woodley, starring Edmund Kingsley, Jack Gordon and Karen Bryson.
The tone is emotional and thought_provoking and intense.